

Profile

An enthusiast Computer Science undergraduate in Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen with strong experience in Machine Learning and Software Engineering projects. Proven academic and curricular achievements and possesses great interpersonal skill and work ethic.

Employment History

Branch Store Manager, ACT Clothing Store, Jakarta

MAY 2018 - JULY 2018

- In charge of operational and customer service
- Create Company's financial statements for daily and weekly sales
- Maintaining a conducive and serious environment for staffs and customers

Python Programmer & Tutor, Go.DevSpace Creative Tech Agency, Jakarta

SEPTEMBER 2020 - NOVEMBER 2021

- Supervise a tutor group for High School and College student
- Create Study Curriculum, Projects and Slides for students
- Developed a time-management and communication skills through daily workloads

Education

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science, Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen, China

SEPTEMBER 2019 - MAY 2023

Experience: University's annual charity program committee

Honor & Award:

1 st place team competition of Computer Engineering "Linux Robot Programming" (2020)

Natural Science, SMA Kristen 1 BPK Penabur, Jakarta

JUNE 2016 - MAY 2019

Indonesia Finest High School in 2019 (Rank 2 in Jakarta, Rank 3 in Indonesia)

Grade: 365 (out of 400)

Activity: Annual Region Scout & Photography committee

Courses

Computer Architecture, Chinese University of Hong Kong

JANUARY 2020 - MAY 2021

Data Structure, Chinese University of Hong Kong

MAY 2021 - AUGUST 2021

Details

Jalan Pinisi Indah 6, 29 Jakarta, 14460 Indonesia +628118822972 ryanchrist98@gmail.com

Links

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Skills

Python

C++

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

Linux

Financial Analysis

Microsoft Office

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Good work ethic

Interpersonal Skills

Effective Time Management

Languages

Indonesian

English

Chinese